{"data":[{"question":"I was angry ________ myself for making such a stupid mistake.","a":"with","b":"of","c":"for","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be angry with sbd\/sth: feeling strong emotions which make you want to shout at someone or hurt them because they have behaved in an unfair, cruel, offensive etc way, or because you think that a situation is unfair, unacceptable.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"They were furious ________ me for not telling them the truth.","a":"with","b":"of","c":"for","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be furious with sbd: very angry.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"This chemical is harmful ________ us.","a":"with","b":"of","c":"for","d":"to","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To be harmful to: causing or likely to cause harm.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The monitor is responsible ________ our form-master ________ the class.","a":"with \/ for","b":"for \/ to","c":"to \/ for","d":"with \/ to","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To be responsible to sbd for sth: having a duty to be in charge of or to look after someone or something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"We were surprised ________ the way he behaves. It was quite out of character.","a":"about","b":"with","c":"at","d":"b & c are correct","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To be surprised at sth: having a feeling of surprise.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"These days everybody is aware ________ the danger of smoking.","a":"about","b":"of","c":"on","d":"for","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To be aware of: if you are aware that a situation exists, you realize or know that it exists.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Are you still upset ________ what I said to you yesterday?","a":"about","b":"of","c":"on","d":"for","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be upset about\/at\/by: unhappy and worried because something unpleasant or disappointing has happened.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"We're short ________ staff in our office at the moment. There aren't enough people to do the work that has to be done.","a":"in","b":"of","c":"at","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To be in short of: if something is short, there is not enough of it.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Scientists and engineers have invented filters and other methods of removing ________ from industrial wastes.","a":"pollute","b":"polluted","c":"pollution","d":"pollutants","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Remove something (noun).\u00a0\n- Pollutant: a substance that makes air, water, soil etc dangerously dirty, and is caused by cars, factories etc.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm sorry ________ the smell in this room. It's just been painted.","a":"about","b":"of","c":"on","d":"with","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be sorry about something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"}]}